{
    "id": "a3083221e48e4b4b998c26711c3536d4",
    "title": "Articles Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "………………….. man is mortal.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "A",
                "The",
                "No article"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I am …………………. university student.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "an",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She goes to the temple in ……………….. mornings.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "the",
                "No article"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Kiran is …………………. best student in the class.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "the",
                "No article"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….. camel is the ship of the desert.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "A",
                "The",
                "No article"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "This book has won ………………….. Booker prize.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "the",
                "No article"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Harishchandra was …………………. honest king.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "an",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I am fond of ………………. classical music.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "the",
                "No article"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I met ..................... boy in the store.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "an",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Gold is ....................... precious metal.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "an",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She returned after ………………….. hour.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "an",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "There is ..................... . institution for ....................... blind in this city.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "an, a",
                "an, the",
                "the, the"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}